# Inkyu Shin | Curriculum Vitae

☑ dlsrbgg33@kaist.ac.kr

I am a second-year Ph.D. student at Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) under the co-supervision of Prof. Kuk-Jin Yoon and Prof. In So Kweon. I earned my B.S and M.S degrees in automotive engineering from Hanyang University(HYU) and KAIST in 2019 and 2021. I was a research intern at NEC Laboratories America, Inc, San Jose, CA (virtual).

## **Research Interests**

My research interests currently lie in computer vision. Specifically, I pursue the goal of effectively processing data and building strong recognition model in computer vision. Followings are my main research topics.

- Semantic Segmentation
- Domain Adaptation and Generalization
- Simulated Learning
- Self-supervised Learning

Ultimately, the purpose of these researches is to apply to a variety of applications (e.g., Autonomous driving, Robot Navigation, AR/VR).

## Research Experience

	NEC Laboratories America, Inc	San Jose, CA (virtual)
O	Research Intern, Supervisor: Yi-Hsuan Tsai.	May 2021 - Aug 2021
_	Korea University	Seoul, Korea
O	Research Intern, Supervisor: Jaegul Choo.	Sep 2018 - Dec 2018
	Hanyang University	Seoul, Korea
O	Research Assistant, Supervisor: Myuong-Ho Sunwoo	Jul 2018 - Aug 2018

**Samsung Electronics** 

Intern, Semi-conductor Test Group.

#### **Education**

0	Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)  AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING Ph.D. degree, Advisor: In So Kweon	Daejeon, Korea 2021-
0	Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)  AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING M.S degree, Advisor: In So Kweon  Master's Thesis: Learning to Scale the Labels for Self-training based Domain Adaptation	Daejeon, Korea 2019–2021

Hanyang University (HYU) Seoul, Korea AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING B.S degree 2013-2019

#### **Publications**

(C: conference / J: journal / P: preprint / \* :equal contributions)

Hwasung, Korea

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018

### International Conference.

 [C7] MM-TTA: Multi-Modal Test-Time Adaptation for 3D Semantic Segmentation Inkyu Shin, Yi-Hsuan Tsai, Samuel Schulter, Bingbing Zhuang, Buyu Liu, Sparsh Garg, In So Kweon, Kuk-Jin Yoon
 Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022

- [C6] UDA-COPE: Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Category-level Object Pose Estimation Taeyeop Lee, Byeong-Uk Lee, Inkyu Shin, Jaesung Choe, Ukcheol Shin, In So Kweon, Kuk-Jin Yoon Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [P1] Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Video Semantic Segmentation Kwanyong Park\*, Inkyu Shin\*, Sanghyun Woo, In So Kweon arXiv, 2021
- [C5] LabOR: Labeling Only if Required for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation Inkyu Shin, Dong-Jin Kim, Jae Won Cho, Sanghyun Woo, Kwanyong Park, In So Kweon International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2021 (Oral)
   - Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2021.
- [C4] Discover, Hallucinate, and Adapt:
   Open Compound Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation
   Kwanyong Park, Sanghyun Woo, Inkyu Shin, In So Kweon
   Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2020

   Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2021.
- [C3] Two-phase Pseudo Label Densification for Self-training based Domain Adaptation Inkyu Shin, Sanghyun Woo, Fei pan, In So Kweon European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020
  - Also presented at "Visual Learning with Limited Labels" Workshops in conjunction with (CVPR), 2020
- [C2] Unsupervised Intra-domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation through Self-Supervision
  Fei pan, Inkyu Shin, Francois Rameau, Seokju Lee, In So Kweon
  Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2020 (Oral)
   Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2020.
- o [C1] Image-to-Image Translation via Group-wise Deep Whitening-and-Coloring Transformation Wonwoong Cho, Sungha Choi, David Keetae Park, Inkyu Shin, Jaegul Choo Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2019 (Oral)

#### **Awards**

2021: Qualcomm Inovation Award.2020: Qualcomm Inovation Award.

#### IT skills

o Languages: Python, MATLAB, C, LATEX

Libraries: PyTorch

# References

- In So Kweon, Professor, KAIST iskweon@kaist.ac.kr
- Kuk-Jin Yoon, Professor, KAIST kjyoon@kaist.ac.kr

# **Service**

o Military Service: Graduated from US Army Sergeant school(WLC) as KATUSA.